Guide to the Time Inc. The March of Time Records 1935-1995 MS 3009-RG 15
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. The March of Time Records
1935-1995
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 15
23 Linear Feet (23 boxes)
The Time Inc. The March of Time Records contain materials used in the production of the radio, film, and television versions of the show as well as in the production of films that The March of Time created for outside organizations. The majority of the materials are related to the film version of the show that was broadcast in theaters from 1935 to 1951.
Historical Note
The March of Time originally debuted on March 6, 1931 as radio newsreel on CBS Radio. The show was developed by Fred Smith, a radio executive, and Roy Larsen while he was the circulation director of Time. The two envisioned the show as a way to dramatize the news and reenact events that could not be reported live. At first, the show focused on domestic stories, but changed its focus at the beginning of World War II and began reporting on international events as well. In 1942, the show switched to providing straightforward news reports which relied on Time correspondents around the world instead of dramatized reenactments. The radio news program continued until 1945.
During The March of Time radio broadcast, Louis De Rochemont, a director of short films for Fox Movietone News, heard the show and had the idea for something he termed "pictoral journalism" which would recreate The March of Time on film. De Rochemont brought his idea to Larsen, and they began work on the film version of The March of Time in June 1934. The first episode of the film version debuted at the Capitol Theatre in New York City on February 1, 1935. While there had been newsreels shown before and between films before this point, their popularity had declined after the advent sound films. The March of Time would update and modernize the newsreels that had previously been seen. Unlike older versions of newsreels that avoided reporting on current events or anything controversial, The March of Time aimed to report events as they happened and included stories found on the pages of Time and Life. The show also included archival footage from the federal governemt, reenactments, interviews, and dramatic voice-overs. As the show matured and expanded, there were fewer reenactments and more interviews. With the rise of television and the costs of production, Time Inc. attempted to reduce the number films of The March of Time in the hope to reduce the costs while allowing the show to still exist. While this strategy did reduce costs, it also reduced profits. Due to budgetery issues, The March of Time newsreels ended in August 1951.
An attempt to relaunch the show was started in 1964. This relaunch would broadcast the show on the television channel WNEW instead of in theaters and was created together with the Metropolitan Broadcasting Company. While the original series provided news about current events, the relaunch appeared to have been about historical events and reused ideas and storylines from the original series. This version of the show did not last long and seems to have ended in 1966.
While in theaters, The March of Time delivered new newsreels on a monthly basis to thousands of theaters across the United States and abroad. At its peak, newsreels provided by The March of Time were played in 13,000 theaters and received forty awards and prizes including two Oscars from the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences. Despite the awards and accolades, The March of Time was only profitable during two years of production, 1938 and 1939. Nevertheless, Time Inc. viewed The March of Time as a worthwhile vehicle to solidify its reputation as a news provider.
Citations:
Doll, Susan. "Introduction to THE MARCH OF TIME." Turner Classic Movies. Accessed October 24, 2018. http://www.tcm.com/this-month/article/343404|0/75th-Anniversary-of-The-March-of-Time.html.
Elson, Robert T., and Duncan Norton-Taylor. 1973. The World of Time Inc.: The Intimate History of a Publishing Enterprise, 1941-1960. New York: Atheneum.
National Radio Hall of Fame. "The March of Time." National Radio Hall of Fame. Accessed October 24, 2018. http://nationalradiohalloffame.com/march_of_time.htm.
Prendergast, Curtis, and Geoffrey Colvin. 1986. The World of Time Inc.: The Intimate History of a Changing Enterprise, 1960-1980. New York: Atheneum.
Scope and Contents
The The March of Time Records contain scripts used in the production of The March of Time for film and radio; production files for films created for other organization by The March of Time; files from television producer Mel Baily during a possible revival or reairing of The March of Time; and videocassettes of The March of Time films, episodes, and clips.
Arrangement
The record group is arranged into four series:
Series I. Scripts
Series II. Commercial Productions
Series III. Mel Baily Files on "Crusade in Europe"
Series IV. Audiovisual
Custodial History
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include contracts and consent forms. Restricted boxes include R40 and R41. Unreformatted audiovisual and digital material in the collection is not accessible. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Related Materials
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Additional records from The March of Time and regarding its history can be found in the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG1).
Continuities.; Dope sheets.; Motion picture journalism; Newsreels; Radio journalism; Radio programs; Radio scripts; Reporters and reporting -- United States; screenplays; Time, inc -- History; Videocassettes; De Rochemont, Louis, 1899-1978; Larsen, Roy E. (Roy Edward), 1899-; March of time (Motion picture); March of time (Radio program)
- Series I. Scripts, 1935-1974; 6 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  The Scripts series contains scripts used in the production of The March of Time for film and radio. Additionally, there are indexes and continuities that provide lists of episodes created, episode titles if they exist, and sometimes summaries of the episodes' contents. The terms index and continuity seem to be used interchangeably and refer to the same type of document.
  Arrangement
  Arranged into two subseries:
  Subseries I.A. Films
  Subseries I.B. Radio.
  - Subseries I.A. Films, 1935-1953, 1974, undated; 5.75 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
    The Films subseries contains the scripts used in the production of the March of Time film series that played in theaters from 1935 through 1951. In addition to the scripts, the sub-series also contains indexes and continuities. The continuities are on microfilm. All other materials in this series are on paper.
    Arranged in original order based on volume and issue numbers with specials at the end.
    - March of Time Continuities: Vol. 1 to Vol. 12 Issues 1-6, 1935-1945 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 1)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "March of Time (Continuities) Roll 1 Vol I to Vol XII, No. 1-6". Also includes a note with film codes and date.
    - March of Time Continuities: Vol. 12 Issue 7 to Vol 17 Issue 6 and Specials, 1945-1951 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 2)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "March of Time (Continuities) Roll 2 Vol XII No 7 to Vol XVII No 1-6 also "Specials" ". Includes a note listing film codes and script titles.
    - Movie Index, undated (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 1 Issues 1-9, 1935 February 1 - 1935 December 13 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 2-10)
    - Vol. 2 Issues 1-8, 1936 January 7 - 1936 August 7 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 11-18)
    - Vol. 3 Issues 1-13, 1936 September 2 - 1937 August 6 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 19-31)
    - Vol. 4 Issues 1-3, 1937 September 10 - 1937 October 29 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 32-34)
    - Vol. 4 Issues 4-13, 1937 November 26 - 1938 August 6 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 1-10)
    - Vol. 5 Issues 1-13, 1938 September 2 - 1939 August (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 11-23)
    - Vol. 6 Issues 1-13, 1939 September - 1940 August (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 24-36)
    - Vol. 7 Issue 1, 1940 September (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 37)
    - Vol. 7 Issues 2-13, 1940 September - 1941 August (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 1-12)
    - Vol. 8 Issues 1-13, 1941 August - 1942 July (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 13-25)
    - Vol. 9 Issues 1-13, 1942 September - 1943 August (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 26-38)
    - Vol. 10 Issues 1-5, 1943 September - 1943 December (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 39-43)
    - Vol. 10 Issues 6-13, 1944 January - 1944 August (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 1-8)
    - Vol. 11 Issues 1-13, 1944 September - 1945 August 10 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 9-21)
    - Vol. 12 Issues 1-13, 1945 September 17 - 1946 August 9 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 22-28)
    - Vol. 13 Issues 1-6, 1946 September 7 - 1947 January 24 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 29-31)
    - Vol. 13 Issues 7-13, 1947 February 21 - 1947 August 8 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 1-4)
    - Vol. 14 Issues 1-18, 1947 September 5 - 1948 December 24 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 5-12)
    - Vol. 15 Issues 1-12, 1949 January 21 - 1949 December 29 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 13-18)
    - Vol. 16 Issues 1-8, 1950 February 3 - 1950 December 22 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 19-22)
    - Vol. 17 Issues 1-6, 1951 February 2 - 1951 August 17 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 23-25)
    - Specials: The Golden Twenties, 1950 April 8 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 26)
    - Specials: The Holy Year at the Vatican, 1950 October 1 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 1)
    - Specials: If Moscow Strikes, 1951 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 2)
    - Specials: The Ramparts We Watch, 1940 August 16 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 3)
    - Specials: The Story of the Vatican, 1941 July 18 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 4)
    - Specials: We are the Marines, 1942 December (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 5)
    - Specials: U.S. Air-force: This is Russia, 1953 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.B. Radio, 1931-1945; .25 Linear Feet (7 reels of microfilm)
    The Radio subseries contains microfilm versions of the scripts used in the production of the radio version of March of Time which broadcast from 1931 through 1945. An index to the episodes is included on the first reel of microfilm. Reel 5, which should include scripts from October 1936 to November 1937, is missing. Materials are dated based on contents and not date of microfilm imaging.
    Arranged by numeric order of reel which is the index followed by scripts in chronological order.
    - Index: Mar. 1931 - July 1945 and Scripts: Mar. 1931 - Dec. 1932, 1931-1945 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 1)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "Roll No. 1 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Index Mar. 1931 - July 1945 Mar. 1931 - Dec. 1932"
    - Scripts: Jan. 1933 - March 1935, 1933-1935 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 2)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "Roll No. 2 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Jan. 1933 to March 1935"
    - Scripts: April 1935 - Feb. 1936, 1935-1936 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 3)
      1 microfilm reels. On label: "Roll No. 3 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts April 1935 to Feb. 1936"
    - Scripts: Mar. 1936 - Sept. 1936 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 4)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "Roll No. 4 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Mar. 1936 to Sept. 1936"
    - Scripts: Dec. 1937 - Nov. 1941, 1937-1941 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 6)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "Roll No. 6 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Dec. 1937 to Nov. 1941"
    - Scripts: Dec. 1941 - Oct. 1943, 1941-1943 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 7)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "Roll No. 7 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Dec. 1941 to Oct. 1943"
    - Scripts: Nov. 1943 to July 1945, 1943-1945 (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 8)
      1 microfilm reel. On label: "Roll No. 8 Time Inc. March of Time Radio Scripts Nov. 1943 to July 1945"
- Series II. Commercial Productions, 1937-1954; 3.5 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
  The Commercial Productions series contains materials related to the production of films that The March of Time created for organizations outside of Time Inc. The creator of the files labeled them "Commercial," but they are not for advertising commercials. These films were usually used to build support for an organization or build morale within a professional organization. The materials contained in this series includes scripts, consent forms, both internal and external correspondence related to the creation and production of the films, lists of actors, lists of set details and supplies, lists of key numbers, cameraman dope sheets, newspaper and magazine clippings, handwritten notes related to changes in film production, purchase orders, bills of service, and lists of music. Only files for A to C are present.
  Arranged in alphabetical order based on the original order.
  - A: Miscellaneous, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 7)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies): Gag Reel, 1938 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 8)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies) and ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): America and Advertising, 1941, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 9)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies) and ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Freedom is Indivisible (Eisenhower), 1948-1949, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 10)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies) and ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Freedom is Indivisible (Eisenhower) [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R40)
  - AGMA (American Grocery Manufacturers Association), 1939 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 11)
  - American Red Cross: A Life in Your Hands, 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 12)
  - American Red Cross: A Life in Your Hands [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R40)
  - American Red Cross: All Together, 1948 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 13)
  - American Red Cross: All Together [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R40)
  - American Red Cross: At His Side, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 14)
  - American Red Cross: At His Side [RESTRICTED], 1944 (Offsite-box R40)
  - American Red Cross: Call to Action, 1947 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 15)
  - American Red Cross: Call to Action [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R40)
  - American Red Cross: The Job Ahead, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 16)
  - American Red Cross: The Job Ahead [RESTRICTED], 1946 (Offsite-box R40)
  - American Red Cross: Seeing Them Through, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 17)
  - American Red Cross: Since Pearl Harbor, 1943 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 18)
  - American Red Cross: Since Pearl Harbor [RESTRICTED], 1943 (Offsite-box R40)
  - American Red Cross: Your Red Cross, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 19)
  - American Red Cross: Your Red Cross [RESTRICTED], 1954 (Offsite-box R40)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Gag Reel, 1937, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 20)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Out of Today A Better Tomorrow, 1943-1944, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 21)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Out of Today A Better Tomorrow [RESTRICTED], 1941-1943 (Offsite-box R40)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Science in Business, 1939-1940, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 22)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Science in Business [RESTRICTED], 1939 (Offsite-box R40)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Year of Decision, 1945-1946, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 23)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers Inc.): Year of Decision [RESTRICTED], 1945-1949 (Offsite-box R40)
  - A.T. & T: Vote of Confidence, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 24)
  - Auto Accessories, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 25)
  - B: Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 26)
  - Bank of America: California Heritage: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1951-1953, undated (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bank of America: California Heritage: Long Version, 1952-1953, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 27)
  - Bank of America: California Heritage: Long Version [RESTRICTED], 1953 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bank of America: California Heritage: Miscellaneous, 1951-1953, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 28)
  - Bank of America: California Heritage: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1951-1952 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bank of America: California Heritage: Short Version, 1953 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 29)
  - Bank of America: Miscellaneous, 1947-1953 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 30)
  - Bank of America: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bank of America: New California: Legal, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 31)
  - Bank of America: New California: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1948-1949, undated (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bank of America: New California: Long Version, 1948 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 32)
  - Bank of America: New California: Short Version, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 33)
  - Bank of America: New California: Short Version [RESTRICTED], 1949 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bank of America: Stockholders Trailer, 1948-1950, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 34)
  - Benton, 1950, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 1)
  - Bethlehem Steel, 1947, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 2)
  - Bituminous Coal Industry: Legal, 1951 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 3)
  - Bituminous Coal Industry: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Bituminous Coal Industry: Miscellaneous, 1950-1953 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 4-5)
  - Bituminous Coal Industry: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Burlington Mills: Legal, 1950 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 6)
  - Burlington Mills: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1950, undated (Offsite-box R40)
  - Burlington Mills: Miscellaneous, 1950-1951, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 7)
  - Campbell Soup, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 8)
  - Cancer Fund, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 9)
  - Canon Mills [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio: Week-End at White Sulphur: Legal, 1948 (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 10)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio: Week-End at White Sulphur: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1948, undated (Offsite-box R40)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio: Week-End at White Sulphur: Miscellaneous, 1948-1949, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 11)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio: Week-End at White Sulphur: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1948 (Offsite-box R40)
  - Chesterfield, 1940-1944, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 12)
  - Chesterfield [RESTRICTED], 1939, undated (Offsite-box R40)
  - Chesterfield [RESTRICTED], 1939-1943, undated (Offsite-box R41)
  - Chesterfield: Durham: Dopesheets and Key Numbers, 1939-1942, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 13-16)
  - Chesterfield: Durham: "Tobaccoland - U.S.A.", 1939-1943, undated (Offsite-box 2797, Folder 17-19)
  - Chesterfield: Durham: "Tobaccoland - U.S.A." [RESTRICTED], 1942 (Offsite-box R41)
- Series III. Mel Baily Files on "Crusade in Europe", 1945-1965; 1 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
  The Mel Baily Files on "Crusade in Europe" series contains the files accumulated by Mel Baily during the production of the The March of Time relaunch that occurred in the early 1960s by Time-Life Broadcast. Mel Baily was an executive with New York television station WNEW owned by Metropolitan Broadcasting, a producer of the relauch. The majority of files were labeled "Crusade in Europe." Crusade in Europe was a World War II documentary film series based on Dwight D. Eisenhower's book and produced by The March of Time, and originally released in 1949. It is unclear if this series was set to relaunch, if it was part of a new series, or if it was a template for the new series. Materials include scripts, sequence cards, purchase orders, contracts, correspondence related to the use of music and archival film footage, research materials, and music catalogs.
  Arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Contracts, 1964, undated (Offsite-box R41)
  - Expenditures, 1964-1965, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 1-2)
  - Hitler Narrative, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 3)
  - Music, 1964, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 4)
  - Optical Film House, 1962-1964, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 5)
  - Research Documents, 1945 (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 6)
  - Show #2 Sequence Cards, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 7)
  - Show #3 Sequence Cards, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 8)
  - Show #4 Sequence Cards, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 9)
  - Scripts, undated (Offsite-box 2798, Folder 10-11)
- Series IV. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1979-1995, undated; 12.5 Linear Feet (13 boxes)
  The Audiovisual series contains videocassettes related to The March of Time. The majority of tapes include episodes of The March of Time but some tapes, such as Time Warner: The Changing Face of Media and Entertainment and the WPA Film Library Sample Reel, only contain clips from the show. Those tapes which include episodes of The March of Time are undated but includes episodes of the show from 1935 to 1951. While the majority of tapes contain tapes from one volume, some tapes include episodes from multiple volumes.
  Subseries IV.A. Internal Use
  Subseries IV.B. Commercially Distributed
  - Subseries IV.A. Internal Use, 1979-1995, undated; 11 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
    The Internal Use subseries contains videocassettes that were created for use within Time Inc. or for preservation purposes. These tapes mainly contain episodes of March of Time but Time Warner: The Changing Face of Media and Entertainment is assumed to contain only clips from The March of Time. While the majority of tapes contain episodes from one volume, some tapes include episodes from multiple volumes.
    Arranged in their original order by volume number and with special releases at the end. If a tape includes episodes from multiple volumes then that tape is placed with the earliest volume on the tape.
    - Untitled, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in.
    - Untitled, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 2)
    - March of Time: Vol. 1 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 1 #1 Vol 2 #2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 1 Issues 1-2, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 1 #1 Vol 1 #2"
    - March of Time: Vol. 1 Issues 5-6, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 1 Ep 5/6"
    - March of Time: Vol. 1 Issues 7-8, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 1 #7 Vol 1 #8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 1 Issues 7-8, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 1 #7 Vol 1 #8"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issues 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 2 #4 Vol 2 #5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issues 4-5, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Vol 2 #4/5"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): 3/4 in. On case label and cassette label: "March of Time Volume #2 Episode #6 Volume #2 Episode #7"
    - March of Time: Vol. 2 Issues 6-7, undated (Offsite-box 2799, Item 11)